bapugunda.com 2013-03-09

# Novalayer.com | Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

In an effort to protect our clients' and site visitors' privacy and rights, NovaLayer has established a thorough Privacy Policy which explains what information is gathered on visitors and how we deal with that information. We advise all visitors and clients to read and understand our privacy policy, and to check it periodically for any updates or revisions. If you have any questions about the contents of our statement, contact us through email (support@novalayer.com) and we would be happy to answer any querie you may have. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which NovaLayer collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of this our website. Our sites use several different forms that our customers can use to request information, products, and services. From these forms, we collect the following information:

\- Visitors' contact information (such as e-mail addresses, name, telephone, number, and postal address)   
\- Unique identifiers (such as customer numbers)   
\- Financial information (such as credit card numbers)   
\- IP addresses 

**Privacy**   
Users' privacy is of supreme importance to NovaLayer. NovaLayer is committed to safeguarding the information Users entrust to NovaLayer.

**The Information We Collect**   
NovaLayer may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. NovaLayer may also collect information about how Users use our Web site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the website or the domains from which Users originate. We may use "cookies" to track how Users use our Web site. A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on the Users' PC and use to identify the User should they visit the Web site again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our Web site.

**How We Use Information**   
We use your contact information to send you information about our company, process requests for services, send invoices, and to contact you when necessary. We also use the information we collect to improve the content of our web site. You will not receive any communications from us unless you specifically request us to send you information and provide us with a method to contact you such as telephone or email address. Existing customers cannot opt-out of receiving information that we deem important for us to communicate in order to provide ongoing services and support. Customers can update contact information on at any time by sending an email to either billing@novalayer.com or support@novalayer.com.

**Disclosure of Information**   
NovaLayer will not disclose information about customers or a visitor without the express permission of the customer unless the release of this information is required to satisfy an action requested by the customer or is required by a government or law enforcement authority. However, we reserve the right to transfer information collected from our customers in connection with any future transaction involving the transfer of the assets of our company.

**Maintenance of Information**   
Information about Users that is maintained on our systems is protected using industry standard security measures. However, we cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure.

**Questions  
** Users may direct questions concerning this statement by e-mail to: support@novalayer.com. Users may elect not to receive solicitations from NovaLayer or from trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners by letting us know. Updated January 15, 2011 NovaLayer.com 

E-mail: admin [at] novalayer.com
